<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jump into Bitcoin Ordinals on Ordinals Ecosystem</title>
    <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jump into Bitcoin Ordinals on Ordinals Ecosystem</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2023, Ordinals Ecosystem</copyright><atom:link href="https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bitcoin Network</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/learn/bitcoin-101/bitcoin-network/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/learn/bitcoin-101/bitcoin-network/</guid>
      <description>Bitcoin mining is a process where powerful computers solve complex mathematical problems to validate transactions on the blockchain. The blockchain is a decentralized ledger that records all Bitcoin transactions, which ensures that transactions are secure and tamper-proof. When a user initiates a transaction, it is broadcasted to the Bitcoin network, where it is picked up by miners. Miners then validate the transaction by solving a complex mathematical problem that requires significant computing power.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/learn/bitcoin-101/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/learn/bitcoin-101/faq/</guid>
      <description>Bitcoin What is Bitcoin? Bitcoin is a decentralized digital currency that was created in 2009 by an unknown person using the name Satoshi Nakamoto. How does Bitcoin work? Bitcoin works through a decentralized network of computers that use a public ledger called the blockchain to keep track of transactions. When someone sends Bitcoin to someone else, the transaction is verified by computers on the network and added to the blockchain. Once the transaction is added to the blockchain, it is considered to be confirmed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magic Eden on Bitcoin</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/magic-eden/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/magic-eden/</guid>
      <description>Magic Eden is the leading community-centric NFT marketplace. Magic Eden is a popular online marketplace for buying and selling NFTs. They recently integrated Bitcoin Ordinals, which means users can now connect their Bitcoin wallet to the platform and trade NFTs.
The marketplace is designed to be user-friendly and accessible to everyone. The platform features an intuitive interface that makes it easy to browse and purchase NFTs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ordinals Wallet</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordinals-wallet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordinals-wallet/</guid>
      <description>Ordinals Wallet is a completely trustless, non-custodial wallet and marketplace Ordinals Wallet provides a secure and user-friendly solution for receiving, storing, and viewing Ordinals in your wallet.
One of the unique aspects of Ordinals Wallet is its popular Ordinals marketplace, which enables users to list Ordinals for sale and make purchases. This means that you can not only hold onto your Ordinals but also trade them with others, expanding your portfolio and potentially earning a profit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UniSat</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/unisat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/unisat/</guid>
      <description>UniSat Wallet is a browser extension wallet to help you store, send, and receive Bitcoin and Ordinals. As the world&amp;rsquo;s first Open Source Chrome wallet for Ordinals, it offers a range of features that make it an ideal choice for anyone looking for a secure and reliable wallet.
When it comes to security, UniSat is a non-custodial wallet, which means that you&amp;rsquo;re always in control of your funds. UniSat Wallet never has access to your funds, and it never stores your seed phrase, password, or any private information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ord.io</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ord-io/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ord-io/</guid>
      <description>Ord.io is a user-friendly Ordinals Explorer with goal to create the best experience for you to share your favorite inscriptions with others. It&amp;rsquo;s packed with interesting features.
Inscriptions are passed through a computer program that can identify and tag them with relevant labels. This program uses object recognition technology to analyze the inscriptions and determine what they say or represent.
If you have an ordinal inscription in your wallet, you can vote for inscriptions by either giving them a thumbs up or a thumbs down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ordinal Hub</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordinal-hub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordinal-hub/</guid>
      <description>Ordinal Hub allows you to keep up with the latest and most popular collections of Ordinal inscriptions. Stay informed about the latest releases and trends in this emerging field of Bitcoin. With this information, you can stay ahead of the curve and be among the first to discover and collect new mints.
Ordinal Hub also has a block explorer which allows you to explore inscriptions on the blockchain. This can help you learn more about how inscriptions work and discover new and interesting ones that you may not have seen before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ordinals.com</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordinals-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordinals-com/</guid>
      <description>Ordinals.com is the Ordinals Explorer built by the creator of the Ordinals protocol. Ordinals.com is a user-friendly Ordinals Explorer which lets you easily search for Ordinal inscriptions. The website also features a handbook that let&amp;rsquo;s you gain insights into the technical intricacies of the Ordinals protocol. It is the perfect resource for anyone looking to deepen their understanding of this new technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>XVerse</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/xverse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/xverse/</guid>
      <description>The most advanced Bitcoin wallet, built for everyone. XVerse Wallet is a secure and reliable wallet to store your Bitcoins. You can access your wallet through your desktop or mobile device, making it easy to manage your transactions on the go.
The wallet&amp;rsquo;s intuitive design makes it simple for beginners to navigate and use, while its advanced features offer more experienced users the flexibility and control they need.
Whether you&amp;rsquo;re new to Bitcoin or an experienced user, XVerse Wallet is the perfect choice for anyone looking for the most advanced and user-friendly Bitcoin wallet on the market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luminex</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/luminex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/luminex/</guid>
      <description>Find the rarest Ordinals from both Bitcoin and Ethereum and start your journey to owning one-of-a-kind Ordinals! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenOrdex</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/openordex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/openordex/</guid>
      <description>OpenOrdex is an open source zero-fee trustless Bitcoin NFT marketplace based on partially signed bitcoin transactions </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ordinals Bot</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordinals-bot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordinals-bot/</guid>
      <description>With Ordinals Bot it&amp;rsquo;s easy to create Ordinals inscriptions on Bitcoin. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ordynals</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordynals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordynals/</guid>
      <description>Ordynals helps you explore ordinal inscriptions. With its block explorer you can easily navigate through inscriptions and see their details. Ordynals has a floor tracker that shows you an overview of the floor prices of the top collections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ord City</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordcity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordcity/</guid>
      <description>An online marketplace for Ordinal Inscription NFTs. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OrdinalSafe</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordinal-safe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordinal-safe/</guid>
      <description>OrdinalSafe is a Bitcoin extension wallet built for Ordinals </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gamma</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/gamma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/gamma/</guid>
      <description>Gamma enables the trading of Bitcoin NFTs using Ordinals on L1 and Stacks on L2. Gamma consists of three parts:
Inscribe tool for creators to easily make their own Ordinals NFTs. Marketplace where people can browse and buy Ordinals NFTs. API Infrastructure that lets other apps and services use Gamma&amp;rsquo;s features. Most of the NFT collections on Gamma were made using the inscribe tool, and lots of money has been exchanged through the marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generative</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/generative/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/generative/</guid>
      <description>Generative is next generation art marketplace on Bitcoin network with the mission to bring generative art to every home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hiro Wallet</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/hiro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/hiro/</guid>
      <description>Hiro Wallet is the most popular and trusted wallet for apps built on Bitcoin. The Hiro Wallet is a great tool that helps you manage your tokens and collectibles on Bitcoin and Bitcoin L2s, while also keeping them safe when you use different apps.
Hiro Wallet provides all the necessary features you need for managing your assets directly from your browser.
Create Ordinal inscriptions. Send bitcoin to any type of Bitcoin address.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ordinals Finance</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordinals-finance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordinals-finance/</guid>
      <description>Ordinals Finance is a platform for developing DeFi applications on Bitcoin Ordinals Finance is a platform for decentralized finance (DeFi) that aims to create a more accessible, transparent, and secure financial system for individuals and communities worldwide. It is their goal is to become a leading DeFi platform that is easy to use and available to everyone, regardless of their financial background or location.
By leveraging the Bitcoin blockchain, Ordinals Finance aims to develop innovative DeFi applications that can help address the traditional financial system&amp;rsquo;s major challenges, such as high fees, lack of transparency, and limited credit access.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ordinals Market</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordinals-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordinals-market/</guid>
      <description>Ordinals Market is a platform that allows people to trade Bitcoin inscriptions on the Ethereum blockchain. Bitcoin inscription trading can sometimes be difficult because of the slow speed of the Bitcoin network. To solve this problem, Ordinals Market stores each inscription in a secure vault, which is an ERC-721 token on the Ethereum blockchain.
The vault has the encrypted private keys to the Bitcoin address that owns the inscription. The owner can open the vault at any time, decrypt the private keys, and claim the inscription directly on the Bitcoin network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ordswap</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordswap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordswap/</guid>
      <description>Ordswap is the world&amp;rsquo;s first and largest trustless Ordinals marketplace built on Bitcoin. Ordswap is an online marketplace that specializes in the buying, selling, and inscribing of Bitcoin Ordinals. As the first trustless ordinal NFT marketplace, Ordswap offers an all-in-one solution for everything Ordinals, making it easy for collectors and creators to get started with their NFT trading.
By using PSBT, users can complete their transactions without having to worry about expensive fees or complicated processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ORDX</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordx/</guid>
      <description>ORDX is the safest Ordinals marketplace built on Bitcoin. ORDX is an online marketplace that specializes in the buying and selling of inscriptions using Bitcoin.
When you buy or sell an inscription on ORDX, you can be sure that everything is done in a transparent way, without any need for a middleman or trusted third party. This means you can have peace of mind knowing that your transactions are safe and secure.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
