<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>explorer on Ordinals Ecosystem</title>
    <link>http://ordinals-ecosystem.com/tags/explorer/</link>
    <description>Recent content in explorer on Ordinals Ecosystem</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2023, Ordinals Ecosystem</copyright><atom:link href="http://ordinals-ecosystem.com/tags/explorer/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ordinals Wallet</title>
      <link>http://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordinals-wallet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordinals-wallet/</guid>
      <description>Ordinals Wallet is a completely trustless, non-custodial wallet and marketplace Ordinals Wallet provides a secure and user-friendly solution for receiving, storing, and viewing Ordinals in your wallet.
One of the unique aspects of Ordinals Wallet is its popular Ordinals marketplace, which enables users to list Ordinals for sale and make purchases. This means that you can not only hold onto your Ordinals but also trade them with others, expanding your portfolio and potentially earning a profit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UniSat</title>
      <link>http://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/unisat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/unisat/</guid>
      <description>UniSat Wallet is a browser extension wallet to help you store, send, and receive Bitcoin and Ordinals. As the world&amp;rsquo;s first Open Source Chrome wallet for Ordinals, it offers a range of features that make it an ideal choice for anyone looking for a secure and reliable wallet.
When it comes to security, UniSat is a non-custodial wallet, which means that you&amp;rsquo;re always in control of your funds. UniSat Wallet never has access to your funds, and it never stores your seed phrase, password, or any private information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ord.io</title>
      <link>http://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ord-io/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ord-io/</guid>
      <description>Ord.io is a user-friendly Ordinals Explorer with goal to create the best experience for you to share your favorite inscriptions with others. It&amp;rsquo;s packed with interesting features.
Inscriptions are passed through a computer program that can identify and tag them with relevant labels. This program uses object recognition technology to analyze the inscriptions and determine what they say or represent.
If you have an ordinal inscription in your wallet, you can vote for inscriptions by either giving them a thumbs up or a thumbs down.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ordinal Hub</title>
      <link>http://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordinal-hub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordinal-hub/</guid>
      <description>Ordinal Hub allows you to keep up with the latest and most popular collections of Ordinal inscriptions. Stay informed about the latest releases and trends in this emerging field of Bitcoin. With this information, you can stay ahead of the curve and be among the first to discover and collect new mints.
Ordinal Hub also has a block explorer which allows you to explore inscriptions on the blockchain. This can help you learn more about how inscriptions work and discover new and interesting ones that you may not have seen before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ordinals.com</title>
      <link>http://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordinals-com/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordinals-com/</guid>
      <description>Ordinals.com is the Ordinals Explorer built by the creator of the Ordinals protocol. Ordinals.com is a user-friendly Ordinals Explorer which lets you easily search for Ordinal inscriptions. The website also features a handbook that let&amp;rsquo;s you gain insights into the technical intricacies of the Ordinals protocol. It is the perfect resource for anyone looking to deepen their understanding of this new technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luminex</title>
      <link>http://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/luminex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/luminex/</guid>
      <description>Find the rarest Ordinals from both Bitcoin and Ethereum and start your journey to owning one-of-a-kind Ordinals! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenOrdex</title>
      <link>http://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/openordex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/openordex/</guid>
      <description>OpenOrdex is an open source zero-fee trustless Bitcoin NFT marketplace based on partially signed bitcoin transactions </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ordinals Bot</title>
      <link>http://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordinals-bot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordinals-bot/</guid>
      <description>With Ordinals Bot it&amp;rsquo;s easy to create Ordinals inscriptions on Bitcoin. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ordynals</title>
      <link>http://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordynals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordynals/</guid>
      <description>Ordynals helps you explore ordinal inscriptions. With its block explorer you can easily navigate through inscriptions and see their details. Ordynals has a floor tracker that shows you an overview of the floor prices of the top collections.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hiro Wallet</title>
      <link>http://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/hiro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/hiro/</guid>
      <description>Hiro Wallet is the most popular and trusted wallet for apps built on Bitcoin. The Hiro Wallet is a great tool that helps you manage your tokens and collectibles on Bitcoin and Bitcoin L2s, while also keeping them safe when you use different apps.
Hiro Wallet provides all the necessary features you need for managing your assets directly from your browser.
Create Ordinal inscriptions. Send bitcoin to any type of Bitcoin address.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
