<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>marketplace on Ordinals Ecosystem</title>
    <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/tags/marketplace/</link>
    <description>Recent content in marketplace on Ordinals Ecosystem</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2023, Ordinals Ecosystem</copyright><atom:link href="https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/tags/marketplace/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Magic Eden on Bitcoin</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/magic-eden/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/magic-eden/</guid>
      <description>Magic Eden is the leading community-centric NFT marketplace. Magic Eden is a popular online marketplace for buying and selling NFTs. They recently integrated Bitcoin Ordinals, which means users can now connect their Bitcoin wallet to the platform and trade NFTs.
The marketplace is designed to be user-friendly and accessible to everyone. The platform features an intuitive interface that makes it easy to browse and purchase NFTs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ordinals Wallet</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordinals-wallet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordinals-wallet/</guid>
      <description>Ordinals Wallet is a completely trustless, non-custodial wallet and marketplace Ordinals Wallet provides a secure and user-friendly solution for receiving, storing, and viewing Ordinals in your wallet.
One of the unique aspects of Ordinals Wallet is its popular Ordinals marketplace, which enables users to list Ordinals for sale and make purchases. This means that you can not only hold onto your Ordinals but also trade them with others, expanding your portfolio and potentially earning a profit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Luminex</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/luminex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/luminex/</guid>
      <description>Find the rarest Ordinals from both Bitcoin and Ethereum and start your journey to owning one-of-a-kind Ordinals! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenOrdex</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/openordex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/openordex/</guid>
      <description>OpenOrdex is an open source zero-fee trustless Bitcoin NFT marketplace based on partially signed bitcoin transactions </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ord City</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordcity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordcity/</guid>
      <description>An online marketplace for Ordinal Inscription NFTs. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gamma</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/gamma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/gamma/</guid>
      <description>Gamma enables the trading of Bitcoin NFTs using Ordinals on L1 and Stacks on L2. Gamma consists of three parts:
Inscribe tool for creators to easily make their own Ordinals NFTs. Marketplace where people can browse and buy Ordinals NFTs. API Infrastructure that lets other apps and services use Gamma&amp;rsquo;s features. Most of the NFT collections on Gamma were made using the inscribe tool, and lots of money has been exchanged through the marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generative</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/generative/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/generative/</guid>
      <description>Generative is next generation art marketplace on Bitcoin network with the mission to bring generative art to every home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ordinals Finance</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordinals-finance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordinals-finance/</guid>
      <description>Ordinals Finance is a platform for developing DeFi applications on Bitcoin Ordinals Finance is a platform for decentralized finance (DeFi) that aims to create a more accessible, transparent, and secure financial system for individuals and communities worldwide. It is their goal is to become a leading DeFi platform that is easy to use and available to everyone, regardless of their financial background or location.
By leveraging the Bitcoin blockchain, Ordinals Finance aims to develop innovative DeFi applications that can help address the traditional financial system&amp;rsquo;s major challenges, such as high fees, lack of transparency, and limited credit access.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ordinals Market</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordinals-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordinals-market/</guid>
      <description>Ordinals Market is a platform that allows people to trade Bitcoin inscriptions on the Ethereum blockchain. Bitcoin inscription trading can sometimes be difficult because of the slow speed of the Bitcoin network. To solve this problem, Ordinals Market stores each inscription in a secure vault, which is an ERC-721 token on the Ethereum blockchain.
The vault has the encrypted private keys to the Bitcoin address that owns the inscription. The owner can open the vault at any time, decrypt the private keys, and claim the inscription directly on the Bitcoin network.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ordswap</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordswap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordswap/</guid>
      <description>Ordswap is the world&amp;rsquo;s first and largest trustless Ordinals marketplace built on Bitcoin. Ordswap is an online marketplace that specializes in the buying, selling, and inscribing of Bitcoin Ordinals. As the first trustless ordinal NFT marketplace, Ordswap offers an all-in-one solution for everything Ordinals, making it easy for collectors and creators to get started with their NFT trading.
By using PSBT, users can complete their transactions without having to worry about expensive fees or complicated processes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ORDX</title>
      <link>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordx/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ordinals-ecosystem.com/ecosystem/ordx/</guid>
      <description>ORDX is the safest Ordinals marketplace built on Bitcoin. ORDX is an online marketplace that specializes in the buying and selling of inscriptions using Bitcoin.
When you buy or sell an inscription on ORDX, you can be sure that everything is done in a transparent way, without any need for a middleman or trusted third party. This means you can have peace of mind knowing that your transactions are safe and secure.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
